Kettle and Idol
Range
Ever since I was a little girl, I have always loved sleep,
Mr. Tonooka often travels by car,
I sleep whenever I have free time in the car.
You can sleep anywhere?
Yes, I sleep anywhere. I sleep anywhere.
I also have trouble getting up in the morning,
I have to set my alarm an hour in advance to wake up.
I can't hear the alarm,
Mr. Tonooka, a house is a house,
When we come to Tokyo, there is a house where we all stay together.
When we were all sleeping there, my alarm would go off,
When we were all sleeping there, my alarm would go off.
But I couldn't hear it,
There was a girl named Hikaru Richiki, who was in the big bureau,
She didn't wake up very well either,
She was so annoyed by my alarm that she came to stop me,
My alarm was ringing, but I couldn't wake up at all.
That's how much sleep I get.
Do you always have a certain member who wakes you up?
I always sleep with Karin next to me,
Kalin wakes me up when she says, "Pearl, it's almost time for you to go to sleep.
Do you let them sleep until the very last minute?
Yes, I do. She also sleeps until the end of her life.
Who is the member who always wakes up the earliest?
Waka Yasumori and Reine Kitami.
I don't know about those two.
I don't know when they wake up. I mean, they are finished with their makeup when they wake up.
I was like, "What? I thought, "Wow, that's amazing.
I think they used to be able to sleep anywhere,
Have you ever had an episode where you fell asleep in such a place?
When I was in elementary school, I didn't mean to fall asleep,
When I was in elementary school, I didn't mean to fall asleep, but I fell asleep and found myself in the nurse's office,
But my mom told me I wasn't getting enough sleep, and she got mad at me,
I don't remember it at all, so I thought I went to the nurse's office because I wasn't feeling well,I don't remember anything at all, so I thought I might have gone to the infirmary because I was sick,
But it turns out that I didn't get enough sleep.
Lack of sleep?
What? I don't know what's going on.
I sleep a lot.
Now that you mention that you sleep a lot, I wonder where you get the time to read manga.
I read manga on my cell phone.
But when he finishes reading on his cell phone, he goes to bed? Is that how you feel?
Yes, I do. I read manga before going to bed,
I read the manga before going to bed, and then I realized that the next one wasn't going to be updated.
So I said, "Let's go to bed," and went to bed.
Do you fall asleep?
I don't fall asleep.
I definitely want to sleep in a futon,
That's why I take a bath early.
After I finish everything, I like to relax on the futon and read manga,
So I never fall asleep.
As you get older, there are some people who can't fall asleep even after taking a bath.
Most of them?
You know, the other day, Slam Dunk was released as a movie.
I was really looking forward to it so much that for the first time I couldn't sleep that day,
I am the type of person who can sleep the day before a production,
I am the type of person who can sleep at all the day before a production, but I was so surprised that I stayed up until about 3:00 a.m.,
I was surprised and stayed up until about 3:00 a.m. I went to bed and woke up at 4:00 a.m., then went back to bed and woke up at 5:00 a.m. This was my first time.
It was a slam dunk movie.
That's right.
There is no such thing as a live show that you get up for.
But I was really looking forward to it.
So I stayed up late at that time.
Unyunyunyunyunyunyun.
Unyan-unyan-unyan
Nighttime and idols
I thought it might be a little bit dangerous to say that.
I try not to say too much. In front of the members.
I don't want to say I've never been here.
This program isThis program is
Mana-chan
Donkey
Amamii
Tomutan
Rinomaru-chan
Thank you to all of you!
Thank you, everyone!